ilovelupe.com 2014-04-01

# Little Lupe Fuentes - Privacy Policy

## I LOVE LUPE PRIVACY STATEMENT

Lupe Fuentes LLC ("I Love Lupe") is committed to protecting the privacy of users of ILOVELUPE.COM. Because it is a commercial web site, your expectation of privacy is substantially attenuated in comparison with other kinds of web sites. By accessing, browsing or using ILOVELUPE.COM, and by accepting its Terms and Conditions, you acknowledge that you read, understand, and agree to the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not access, browse, or use the ILOVELUPE.COM. 

**1\. How do you use my personal information?**

When you use I LOVE LUPE, we may capture data about which browser and which version of your browser you are using, your operating system, your screen resolution, your path through our site and services, the way you use our Service, and your IP Address.. We use this information in statistical form to assess the patterns in which our members use the site, to make our site appear in its optimal form on your screen, and to make planning and marketing and technical decisions. As a Nonsubscriber or Member of our Site, you may choose to choose to send ILOVELUPE.COM personal information (e.g., your name, mailing address, cellphone number, telephone number, e-mail address), for example, when you send a customer service question. We also use your personal information to help us deliver services.. With the information described, we can assess and fix problems, learn what interests our members, communicate with you and your contacts, enforce our Terms of Service, and help protect you and ILOVELUPE.COM against dishonest schemes, frauds, errors, and crimes. We will use personal information about you to tailor your experience with ILOVELUP.COM to fit you. We may tailor and target our delivery of banners, advertising, and other promotional materials to fit you as you tell us about yourself and your interests. Your email address will be used by us to notify you of interesting news and developments and to verify that you are the person you claim to be in your registration. We may also harvest your email address for commercial purposes and provide it in list form to commercial interests who may solicit you with exciting and interesting solicitations, and maybe some that aren't so exciting and interesting, and we will do this for compensation. When we commercially sell or lease or license lists containing your email address to email advertisers, and when we distribute this information, it may be associated with any other personal information that you have told us about yourself or which we have learned by tracking your use of our web site. We may use any personal information, in any fashion, in any format or analysis or combination with any other data, for any reasonable business purpose. You consent to receiving email from us and from our associates and business partners as your opt-in of their advertising materials under the CAN-SPAM Act. We may also use IP addresses and compare them with username/password combinations in order to detect compromised combinations which may be used fraudulently and to assess the number of locations from which you access our website. We may fully co-operate with law enforcement at any level by assisting them and disclosing any of the personal information described in this Statement or any other information we may know about you, without prior notice to you. Similarly, we will comply with all lawful subpoenas or court orders. We may provide access to personal information to contractors and employees and others working with us to diagnose and repair problems or to optimize the functionality of the Services. We use e-mail to respond to e-mail messages from you, to confirm service orders placed online and to engage in other communication that you have authorized or that we have determined necessary to more effectively service you and our customers. An authorized representative of ILOVELUPE.COM may gain access to your account and the information and data it contains for any reasonable business purpose. 

**2\. Is My Personal Information Secure When It Travels Via the Internet?**

All financial information exchanged with our Billing Processor travels through their security protocols and we believe those to be quite secure; however, they, not us, guarantee the security of that information. We do not encrypt or otherwise secure normal traffic using our web site. The possibility of interception, lawful or otherwise, cannot be excluded when data moves in this fashion. When you submit personal information, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in another country, which may not provide privacy protections similar to those your country provides. 

**3\. Does Your Site Use Cookies?:**

The term "cookie" refers to files that are transferred from a Website to your computer's hard drive. ILOVELUPE.COM uses cookies in order to determine if you are a valid subscribing member, and to track the web site from which you entered our site, the pages you visit, the files your download and their filesize, the time you spend on the various pages, the advertising which you select or click on, and the various other means by which you express interest in the different offerings of our web site. Some of this information may be stored on our servers and other information (including your username and password combination) may be collected and placed on your own computer as a cookie and may be accessed by us or our business partners to tailor advertising for your interest of for any other lawful business purpose. 

**4\. Do You Share Data?**

We may share data information about you with our customers, partners, and advertisers for any reasonable business purpose. If the business that owns ILOVELUPE.COM is sold or acquired, or transferred in any way, all the data, including your personal information, can be expected to go with it to the purchaser. Similarly, if through acquisition or merger the ownership changes, the new owners will have access to this information. Finally, if business assets are sold, transferred, or otherwise conveyed, the persons who receive the benefit of these transactions will also have access to this information. 

**5\. Is My Data Secure?**

There is always a possibility that strangers may hack into servers or otherwise intercept your data and your communications and abuse the data they harvest. We do not assure, and you cannot expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect through ILOVELUPE.COM. Despite all of its best efforts, we do not and cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be obtained illegally from our systems or the routes of Internet distribution, and you agree to assume all risk and liability arising from your use of our services, including the risk of a breach in the security of our systems. ILOVELUPE cannot guarantee and has no control over the public or third party network through which you send your personal information nor the telecommunications networks connected to our site. 

**6\. How Do You Deal With Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of children is vitally important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of ILOVELUPE.COM is structured to attract anyone under 18. 

**7\. What About Links on Your Web Site?**

This web site provides hyperlinks that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or to other Websites not controlled by ILOVELUPE. These hyper-linked Websites may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. ILOVELUPE is not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected through these Websites, and ILOVELUPE expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure. 

**8\. How Do I Correct Or Amend My Information?**

In some cases we honor requests from you to correct or amend your account information (for example, your name or address). You may verify that appropriate corrections have been made. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You will find our contact information below. 

**9\. How Do You Make Changes to This Privacy Policy?**

We can change our Privacy statement at any time for any reason or for no reason, with or without advance notice by posting the changes on ILOVELUPE.COM. They become effective at the time they are posted. Our Agreement with members may be changed under the policies provided for in the Terms of Service as posted on ILOVELUPE.COM, and as they may be changed in conformity with their terms. 

**10\. How To Contact Us?**

Should you have other questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [webmaster@ilovelupe.com](mailto:webmaster@ilovelupe.com?subject=Website:%20Privacy%20Policy), or write to us at: 

**4570 Van Nuys Blvd. # 373 Sherman Oaks, CA 91403**
